[{"answer": "What have you done with those plans", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "If this is a consular ship... were is the Ambassador", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He knew my father", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, sir. I think those new droids are going to work out fine. In fact, I, uh, was also thinking about our agreement about my staying on another season. And if these new droids do work out, I want to transmit my application to the Academy this year", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's what you said last year when my friend and my friend left", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It looks like I'm going nowhere. I have to finish cleaning those droids", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Ob", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, he's not dead, not... not yet", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We don't need to see his identification", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "These are not the droids we're looking for", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "These are not the droids we're looking for", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You can go about your business", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You can go about your business", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Move along. Move along", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Don't insult us. You just watch yourself. We're wanted men. I have the death sentence in twelve systems", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You'll be dead", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Han Solo. I'm captain of the Millennium Falcon. Chewie here tells me you're looking for passage to the Alderaan system", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Fast ship? You've never heard of the Millennium Falcon", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We're caught in a tractor beam! It's pulling us in", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There's nothin' I can do about it, kid. I'm in full power. I'm going to have to shut down. But they're not going to get me without a fight", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "This is not going to work", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I did say so before", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Look out! He's loose", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Go get him", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Ob", "docId": "Star-Wars-A-New-Hope.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Escape is not his plan. I must face him alone", "qsentId": 26}]